目 前 資 金
最 新 余 額
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
人人影視
YYeTs.com
原創翻譯  雙語字幕
■
僅供學習 禁止用于任何商業盈利行為
更多影視更新
請登陸www.YYeTs.com
打工
姐妹花
第六集
第三季
打工
姐妹花
第六集
第三季
\h翻校  狂掉頭發賽太公
\h翻校  失眠暴怒YY貓
后期  灰灰是菇涼\h
時間軸 總監  失眠暴怒YY貓 \h
我結算了小蛋糕店的收銀機
Oh, I closed out the cupcake register.
這是掙來的房租錢
Here's our rent money.
錢拿去  信封袋還我
Gimme back the envelope though,
那袋子也是我的珠寶首飾盒
'cause it's also my jewelry box.
我也結算了收銀機
I closed out the register.
我這也有一份交房租的錢
I have our rent money.
麥克斯  你知道這代表什么嗎
Max, do you know what this means?
如果我腦子沒有被驢踢了
Unless I was hit in the head by a piece of farm equipment,
就表示咱們有盈余啦
it means we have extra money.
我好想來一段盈余慶祝舞
I wanna do the extra money dance,
但我們沒有這一套舞
but we don't have one
因為我們的錢從沒有過盈余
because we've never had extra money!
我唯一會的掙錢[盈余]舞
The only extra money dance I know
需要用到乒乓球
involves ping-pong balls
又名"十八招"  常由東南亞女性表演
由下陰"吞入""噴吐"乒乓球的成人表演
而我也久沒跳  技藝生疏了
and I'm really out of practice.
厄爾  我給你帶來了你的最愛
Earl, I brought you your favorite.
黑人華人混血肚皮舞女嗎
A half-black, half-Chinese belly dancer?
椰子味小蛋糕啦
A coconut cupcake.
你看卡洛琳
Look at Caroline over there.
使出渾身解數跟人調情
She's flirting harder with him
比我對抗心臟病還賣力
than I flirt with heart disease.
不許  不許說
Stop, stop!
人家才看到第一季第二集
I'm only on episode two of season one.
敢說人家打死你
I will kill you!
那...  下回分曉吧
Then... to be continued.
那就是還有下回咩
Oh! It's gonna be continued.
好呀  那我們下回分曉時
Well, then, we will continue this
再來下回分曉吧
when we continue this.
如果你盡全力就這程度
If that's your game,
那估計你這輩子都得跟姐住了  妹子
you're gonna be living with me forever, fran.
他已經連續三晚來我這區
He's been in my section three nights in a row
點火雞肉三明治了
for the turkey club.
我叫他"火雞三明治帥哥"
I'm calling him "the turkey club cutie".
聽得我想"叫救命"
I'm calling poison control.
我看他應該差不多要約我了
I think he's getting ready to ask me out.
他問我是不是住在附近
He wanted to know if I live around here
還問我幾點下班
and what time I get off.
一個愿意等到你下班[高潮]的男人
If a man's gonna wait for you to get off,
絕對要留住啊
he's a keeper.
那就...
So...
下次見啦
See you next time.
那我們就下次見啦
I will see you next time as well.
再見
Bye.
-那是什么  -不知道  我哪會知道
- What's that? - I don't know. How would I know?
因為是你頭上掉下來的啊
Because it came out of your head.
麥克斯  我才沒有去接發
I don't have hair extensions, Max.
好吧  那我拿去扔了
Okay, I'll throw it out.
別  下次能當故事說
No! I'll keep it for this story!
什么故事
What story?
某天晚上我們
The story about how we found
無緣無故發現一段金色接發的故事
a blonde hair extension out of nowhere that night.
超好笑啊
It's hilarious!
是比你大多數故事都好笑了
Well, it's already funnier than most of your stories.
你看  又一段"爆笑故事"
Oh, look, there's another hilarious story!
好啦  麥克斯  我得坦白件事
Okay, Max, I have a confession to make.
我有做過接發
I have hair extensions.
我也有件事想坦白
I also have a confession to make.
我在羅德島殺過人
I murdered a man in Rhode island.
我就接了幾段  讓頭發有點層次
I just have a few. It gives me volume.
可惜它不能讓你有點深度
Too bad it doesn't give you depth.
我現在得想辦法把它們重新接上
Now I have to go and try and reattach these.
這接發不應該這么容易掉啊
These weaves are supposed to last.
我真不敢"接"信會這樣
This is unbe-weave-able!
我在生菜里發現了這個
I found this in the lettuce.
里面有發現陰道避孕環嗎
Any sign of a nuva ring in there?
因為我的不見了
'Cause I can't find mine.
是卡洛琳在掉頭發吧
Caroline's losing her hair, isn't she?
她是不是生病了
Is she sick?
她是不是得了癌癥  得了大"C"[癌]
Does she have cancer, the big "C"?
才不是  小東西
No, little you.
她沒有"大C"
She doesn't have the big "C".
她連"AA"罩杯都沒有
She barely has the double "A"s.
阿憨發現了你的頭發
Han found more of your hair.
他知道我接發的事了嗎
He knows about the extensions?
沒  他以為你得了癌癥
No, he thinks you have cancer.
那就好  沒人知道就好
Oh, good! So no one knows.
安安  姑娘們  今夜因我而性感啦
Hola, ladies! Your night just got sexier.
路易斯  你早就下班了
Luis, you punched out hours ago.
你這么晚還來餐廳干嘛
What are you doing here so late?
回基[家]的路上嗎
On your way homo?
牙尖嘴利呀  小賤人
Good one, hooker!
我在夜店跑攤
No, I'm between clubs.
馬戲夜店現在是直男吧了
Circus just became a straight club,
衛星夜店還得再等半小時  才會變成基吧
And satellite doesn't become a gay club for a half hour.
所以就來跟我兄弟奧列格喝杯雞尾酒啦
So...I'm here to have a cocktail with my bro Oleg.
路易斯  跟你說過他是直男了
Luis, we told you. Oleg is straight.
拜托  我在阿拉巴馬州也是直男
Oh, please! So am I in Alabama.
阿拉巴馬州反對同性戀
學校老師必須教導學生同性戀是違法的
他已經走了
Well, he left already.
我都跟他說我會來坐坐了
But I told him I was gonna stop by.
男人都這樣  懼怕親密感情
Typical man. Fear of intimacy.
卡洛琳兒  趁我過來
Oh, Carolina, while I'm here...
順便把我上班發現的東西還你
This is yours. I found it during my shift.
我沒拿走的小費嗎
Ooh, tips from my tables?
是你沒收好的頭發
More like hair from your head.
我就知道你那頭秀發不可能是真的
I knew this was all too good to be true.
你做了接發
You have extensions.
不是  我是得了癌癥
No, I have cancer.
屁咧  你做了接發  少唬我
No, you have extensions. Good try.
回見
Later!
看出我有何改變嗎
Hey. Notice anything different?
我用小店盈余去弄了新接發
I took some of the extra money and got new hair extensions.
我還給你準備了份禮物  放你房里了
And I also got you a surprise. I put it in your room.
去看看
Go look!
我感興趣的只有大肚豬
I'm not interested unless it's a potbelly pig
打扮成早期移民的大肚豬
or a potbelly pig in a pilgrim costume,
或打扮成大肚豬的早期移民
or a pilgrim in a potbelly pig costume,
或大麻[肚]
or just pot.
提示  我放在你床上哦
Hint, hint. I put it on your bed.
覺得如何  愛不愛啊
What do you think? Do you love?
為啥這坨屎會在我床上
Okay... why is all this crap on my bed?
這他媽是什么玩意啊
And what the hell is it?
這是床裙啊
That's a bed skirt.
我的床才不要穿裙子  它是大老爺們
My bed doesn't wear skirts. It's a dude!
看它在我睡覺時從背后頂我  就知道是爺們
I know, because it pokes me in the back while I'm asleep.
我幫你買了新寢具
I got you new bedding,
幫自己買了套新法蘭絨睡衣
and me some cute new flannel jammies.
上面還有埃菲爾鐵塔的圖案
They have eiffel towers on them.
大家都討厭法國人  所以這衣服超便宜的
They were marked down because everybody hates French people.
這上面連"污漬"都沒有
These don't even have stains!
這樣我怎么知道哪邊是上面
How am I gonna know which is the top now?
麥克斯  這有啥不好
Max, what's the problem?
你的舊床單都用多久了
You've had those old sheets forever.
你連替換的都沒有
You don't even have a spare set.
替換的床單
A spare set of sheets?
你當我誰啊  英國女皇嗎
Who am I, the queen of England?
你真沒勁  氣得我都想扯頭發了
You're so frustrating, I'd pull my hair out...
但我怕不小心扯到接發
But I'm not sure which of it is mine.
你看  這下你高興了嗎
Look! Look! Are you happy?
栗寶都不開心了  他知道我們吵架
Chestnut's upset. He knows we're fighting.
很好
Good!
是該讓他知道哪天他出門買包薯片
He should know that if he goes out for a bag of chips,
很可能一回來
he could come home to find
就發現他的馬鞍被換成丁字褲了
you replaced his saddle with a thong.
我可是送你禮物呢
I got you a present.
你會氣圣誕老人嗎
Would you be this angry at Santa Claus?
他是誰啊
Who's that?
求你了  麥克斯
Max, please.
做點改變  睡在好寢具上面嘛
Just for a change, try sleeping on something nice.
行
Fine!
但我要真想睡在好寢具上面
But if I wanted to sleep on something nice,
我就跟那個搬回家照顧
I would have hooked up with that guy
生病老母親的男人走就好了
who moved home to take care of his sick mother.
小心提防啊  栗寶
Watch your back, Chestnut.
防火防盜防小人
Watch your back.
你個賤人  我的舊寢具呢
Where are my old sheets, bitch?
為什么
Why?
為什么要大半夜罵我賤人
Why are you calling me a "bitch" at night?
人家穿著新睡衣睡覺呢
I was sleeping in my new jammies.
沒我的舊寢具我睡不著
Well, I can't sleep without those sheets.
你所有抽屜我都看過了  你藏哪去了
So where are they? I checked all your drawers.
對了
And by the way,
誰會把電動棒收星巴克杯子里啊
Who hides their vibrator in a Starbucks cup?
明知故問  我繼續睡覺了
You already know the answer, so I'm going back to sleep.
為什么呀
Why!
為什么穿著新睡衣的我會在地上
Why am I on the floor in my new jammies?
到底放哪去了
Where are they?
不在我這  我送給窮人了
I don't have them. I gave them to the poor.
你從窮人那里偷過去的
You took them from the poor!
現在窮人想討回來
And the poor wants them back.
已經遲了
Well, it's too late.
我放到救世軍的慈善捐助箱了
I put them in the Salvation Army donation bin.
那起來  你得去軍中一趟了  賤婦
Well, get up. You're going to the army, bitch.
為什么呀
Whyyyy?
為什么我們大半夜得跑來這里
Why are we here in the middle of the night?
我們要干嘛
What are we doing?
就在這了  跟我過來
Here it is. Come on, follow me.
麥克斯  你要在這殺我嗎
Max, is this where you kill me?
我一直都知道會有這么一天
'Cause I always knew it was gonna happen,
但我不知何時會發生
I just didn't know when.
但這里很有那感覺啊
This feels right though.
我是應該宰了你
I should kill you.
那套寢具對我有很特別的意義好嗎
Those sheets were really special to me, okay?
你在上面失去貞操的嗎
Oh, did you lose your virginities on them?
我不在床上做愛  那是我吃飯的地方
I don't have sex in beds. That's where I eat.
卡洛琳  我有件事要坦白
Caroline, I have a confession.
-什么事  -你有接發
- What is it? - You have hair extensions.
好啦  我說  但你不許看我
Okay, I'll tell you, but look away.
重點是那個枕套  我小時候就開始用了
It's the pillowcase. I've had it since I was a kid.
它又軟又有觸感
It's like soft and nubby
還有邊邊  我可以摸
and it had this edge that I'd like...rub,
在倒霉的日子  也就是每一天
and it relaxed me when things were crappy,
都能讓我放松
which was all the time.
我需要那個枕套才能睡著
I guess I still need that pillowcase to sleep or whatever.
麥克斯  你好可憐哦
Max, that's so sad.
當然可憐啊
Of course it's sad!
我有過歡樂童話故事嗎
When has it ever been a happy tale?
好啦  我得爬進去
All right, I need to crawl in here.
麥克斯  你要爬進這臟箱子啊
Max, you're just gonna crawl into that dirty box?
我們都不知道這箱子有多臟
We don't know where that bin's been.
對了
By the way,
"臟箱子"[臟貨]也是我當年在學校的綽號
"dirty box" was my nickname in continuation school.
幫忙一下
I need help.
你是要我踩你背上  還是踩你的頭
Would you rather I step on your back or your head?
想都別想  這么貴的頭會給你踩嗎
My head? Hardly. Not at these prices.
來吧  十根手指伸出來
Come on, gimme ten fingers.
給過了
I already did.
來的路上伸過十次中指
Behind your back while we were walking here.
是讓你這樣  我就能踩著上去
No, like this, so I can step into it.
就跟個手指籃子一樣
You know, like a finger basket.
手指籃[裝蛋蛋]
Finger basket?
那是你的另一個綽號嗎
Is that another nickname of yours?
不是  但某年夏天本來可以的
No, but for one summer, it could've been.
那算了  來幫忙搬東西讓我踩吧
Forget this, just let me pull this stuff over.
麥克斯  我覺得我們一直在突破下限
Max, I feel like we're not even acknowledging
下限都成路人了
our low points anymore.
麥克斯  千萬小心
Okay, Max, now be very careful.
等我數到...
And on the count of...
你完全能當體操員啊
Wow! You could've been a great gymnast,
如果你有錢  有教練  做了縮胸手術的話
if you'd had money, coaches, and a breast reduction.
你沒事吧
Are you okay?
麥克斯
Max?
發點聲音出來啊
Gonna need some voice contact.
吾路不孤
I'm not in here alone.
你說吾路不孤是個什么意思
What do you mean you're not alone?
意思是  里面不只我一個人
I mean, I'm not in here alone.
別慌  我馬上救你出來
Stay calm! I will get you out of there.
不  我做不到
No, I won't.
我在找打開門的把手
I'm looking for a lever on the inside.
滾出我家
Get outta my house!
我只是想看看你是不是壓在我的枕套上
I just wanna check and see if you're on my pillowcase.
-別啊  麥克斯  -我要我親愛的寢具
- Max, no! - I need my sweet sheets!
放棄吧
Let it go.
如果被他壓在身下了  那也不親不愛了
If your sheets are under there, they're no long sweet.
滾出我家
Get outta my house!
關上門
Close the door!
行行行
Okay! Okay!
真是的  咱倆也算睡過了  真無情
God, sheez. You'd think we'd slept together.
這下我得怎么辦
What am I gonna do?
沒那套寢具我就睡不著
I can't sleep without those sheets.
我恨死你了
I'm so angry at you!
要不是發現這件好奶罩  我會更氣
I'd be even angrier if I hadn't found this great bra.
你想睡覺為啥還要來蘇菲家
Why are you going to Sophie's if you're trying to sleep?
她是我們認識最大嗓門的人了
She's the loudest person we know.
電影院里愛喧嘩的黑人都嫌她吵
Even black people at the movies tell Sophie to be quiet.
我來她家是想要個安眠藥
I am going to Sophie's to get a sleeping pill.
也就是她口中的"晚安糖"
Or as she likes to call them, "night candy".
你不需要吃安眠藥
You don't need a pill.
我有一招很棒的入眠方法
Listen, I have a great sleep technique
是我的睡眠教練教我的
that my sleep coach taught me.
我也跟一堆教練"睡"過
I have slept with my fair share of coaches,
他們的唯一用處就是讓我不能睡
and if anything, they kept me awake.
麥克斯  凌晨三點
Max, it's 3:00 A.M.
正常人應該都睡了
Any normal person is sleeping right now.
姑娘們
Hi, girls.
我一邊聽貓王  一邊拼拼圖呢
Just doing a puzzle and listening to Elvis.
趁你們還沒累累  先來杯酒酒吧
You two want a mai tai before you get too ty-ty?
不用了  但說到累累
No, thanks, but speaking of ty-ty,
我想問你要一顆安眠藥
I was hoping I could snag one of your sleeping pills.
沒問題  我能給你
Oh, sure, I can hook you up.
我從來不用
I never use them.
我晚上都只需要睡三小時
I only need three hours of sleep at night
白天再睡個六小時  進來吧
and six during the day. Come on.
蘇菲
Sophie...
發現哪里是新的嗎
Notice anything new?
有啊
Oh! Yeah!
你頭上接了更多頭發嗎
You planted more hair on your head.
我聽說了
I heard.
麥克斯  你居然告訴她
Max! You told her?
沒  這事都上新聞聯播了
No, it was on CNN.
先報導了敘利亞的新聞
They led with Syria,
然后連續報道了五分鐘你頭發的事
and then did a solid five on your hair.
來啦  藥跟香料
Here we go-- pills and spices!
你有滿香料架的藥嗎
You have a spice rack full of pills?
改天下廚做頓晚餐請我吃吧
You gotta cook me dinner sometime.
我看看
Let's see.
魚油  盤尼西林  阿莫西林
Fish oil, penicillin, amoxicillin...
彩虹糖
Skittles.
這是我的德國神藥
Oh, and this is my German pill
哪天核彈大爆發  還是我被放逐外星時吃
in case they release the bombs or I'm ever abandoned in space.
給  麥克斯  睡個好覺
Here you go, Max. Nighty-night.
這樣吧
Oh, you know what?
管這么多干嘛  老娘也來一粒
What the hell! I'm gonna have one too.
這是睡衣派對
It's a slumber party!
你又有另一架子[胸部]的藥了
Oh, now you got another rack full of pills.
算了吧
Oh, you know what?
別等我了  麥克斯  估計得找一會
Don't wait for me, Max. This might be a while.
麥克斯  你真的得靠藥物嗎
Max, do you really need to take that?
吃完安眠藥  很多人會做怪事
People do weird things on sleeping pills.
我一個朋友
My friend Candice Travelstead
夢游用奶油涂滿皮夾  還打算吃下去
buttered a wallet and tried to eat it.
別擔心  我沒皮夾
Don't worry, I don't have a wallet.
等等  等等
Wait a minute! Wait a minute.
你那顆是安眠藥
Is that the sleeping pill,
還是我的緊急自殺太空藥
or is that my emergency space pill that kills you?
兩種都能讓我閉眼安眠
Either way, I'll get some shut-eye.
麥克斯  不許
Max, no!
不許你拋下我一人在這世界上
You are not gonna die and leave me here alone.
在沒有監護人帶領的情況下  我還沒搞懂
I still don't know how to go east on the "L" Train
怎么坐L火號車去東邊
without a chaperone.
麥克斯  現在是凌晨3點30分
Max, it's 3:30 A.M.,
睡眠教練卡洛琳
and sleep coach Caroline here
最晚能讓你在3點45分安然入睡哦
will have you asleep by 3:45 the latest.
你不是應該泡個熱水澡嗎
You're supposed to be taking a hot bath.
本來是  但當我把塞子塞進去時
I was, but when I put the stopper in,
有東西又把它給頂出來了
something pushed it back out again.
藥片在哪里
Where's that pill?
我藏在身上呢
I've got it on my person,
如果這些都不管用  我就把它給你
and if this doesn't work I'll give it to you.
為了藥片  整只手伸入你洞內找
Oh, I'll go elbow-deep for that pill.
我都會做哦
And don't think I won't.
麥克斯  這是你的新寢具
Max, meet your new sheets.
新寢具  這是...
New sheets, meet--
用不著互相介紹  我又不是神經病人
Don't make me meet the sheets. I'm not a mental patient.
如果我是  那住的地方會比這好多了
If I was, I'd be living in a much nicer place.
而且我所有的枕套都會有花邊
And all my pillowcases would have edges.
哇  你的枕套居然有花邊啊
Wow, even your pillowcase had an edge.
你的枕套到底是什么樣的
What was it like anyway?
就像是你新睡衣下面那樣
It was kinda like the end of your new PJs,
但你的睡衣是我見過最基的東西
but not the queerest thing I've ever seen.
還點蠟燭  你以為我們是女巫嗎
A candle? What are we, witches?
現在想象自己處在一個輕松美麗的地方
Now, imagine yourself in a relaxed, beautiful place.
讓呼吸自由進出
Breathe in and out.
吸氣  呼氣
In and out.
聽著  手指籃姑娘唯一了解的事情
Look, if there's one thing old finger basket know how to do
那就是"進跟出"
it's in and out.
把藥片給我
Gimme the pill.
我還沒說完呢
I'm not finished yet.
但先提醒你
But just so you know,
那顆藥片在一個小時里變色了三次了
that pill has changed colors three times in the last hour.
要么會吃死人  要么就是五彩糖球
So it's either deadly, or an Everlasting Gobstopper.
我真是被你氣死了  你就拿走我唯一一樣
I am so mad at you. You took my one thing.
我生命中有特別意義的東西
That pillowcase was my one special thing.
我的人生中  人們從我身邊拿走了很多東西
In my whole life of people taking things away from me,
唯有那個枕套從來沒人會拿
that was the one thing no one took,
而現在我再也睡不著了
and now I'm never gonna sleep again.
我愛睡覺
And I love sleeping.
做夢是我離有線電視最接近的時刻了
Dreaming is the closest thing I have to cable TV.
夠了  麥克斯
Enough, Max!
在你對"一張床單"[屎]過分依賴的事情上
I've been very patient with this weird attachment you have
我已經夠耐心了
to this little piece of sheet.
你才是"一坨屎"呢
You're a piece of sheet.
在我失去一切時  我懂得兩個道理
Listen, if I learned anything when I lost everything,
那就是  第一
It's that, "A," there's no wiggle room
白干酪的保質期限說到就到了
when it comes to cottage cheese expiration dates,
第二  你不能過于依賴物質事物
And "B," You can't get attached to material things.
得了吧  接發不算嗎
Okay, extensions.
這話什么意思
What does that mean?
意思就是準確來說
It means that your material things
你依賴的事物粘了你滿腦袋
are literally attached to your head.
完全不一樣好嗎
Not the same thing at all.
你滿腦子都是你對那個枕套的依賴
Your dependency on that pillowcase is all in your head,
而你卻不需要它
you don't need it.
那你也不需要這個
Oh. You don't need this.
你欠我14塊
You owe me $14.
先記賬吧
Run a tab.
我才不要坐在這里忍受你的侮辱
I'm not about to sit here and take this abuse
就因為你對一個枕套有著病態的依賴心理
because you have an unhealthy attachment to a pillowcase.
晚安  馬里布芭比
Good night, Malibu Barbie.
希望你不是想要侮辱我
I hope you're not trying to insult me,
因為你這話是在贊美我
because she's gorgeous!
對了  鄭重聲明
And for the record,
我對我的頭發才沒有什么病態的依賴心理
I do not have an unhealthy attachment to my hair.
是嗎
Oh, really.
你個禽獸
You're a monster!
對不起  人家睡不著嘛
I'm sorry, I can't sleep.
只要你把藥片給我  我就沒事了
I'll be fine. Just give me the pill.
只是你心理作用
No! It's all in your head!
快去睡覺
Go to sleep!
我用繩子把門把和我的床綁到一起
I tied the doorknob to my bed with a rope
然后把臥室所有的窗戶都關上了
and locked all the bedroom windows.
你是想傷害我  還是想讓我欲火焚身啊
Are you trying to hurt me or turn me on?
你要做好心理準備  厄爾
Brace yourself, Earl.
麥克斯今天上班的心情不會太好哦
When Max gets here, she will not be in a good mood.
卡洛琳  如果我想跟一群天天好心情的人共事
Caroline, if I wanted to work around people in a good mood,
我早去谷歌上班了
I'd go work at Google.
她從昨天開始就睡不著
She hasn't slept since yesterday
因為我不愿意給她安眠藥  她現在超級火大
and is furious because I won't give her a sleeping pill.
明智之舉
Smart move.
安眠藥只會把人搞得更糟
Sleeping pills mess you up.
我曾經吃過一次  結果在一天后醒來
I took one once, woke up a day later
發現自己科尼島的云霄飛車上
on the roller coaster ride in Coney Island.
我喜歡云霄飛車
I love roller coasters.
但得是坐在座位里我才喜歡啊
Me too, when I'm in a seat.
你們好啊
Oh, hello!
你們倆今晚好嗎
How are you two tonight?
天啊  她太友善了
Oh, no. She's nice.
她肯定從哪里搞到安眠藥了
She must've gotten a pill somewhere.
不  我沒吃藥  只是想明白了
No. No pills. Just had some clarity.
-請跟我來  -好吧
- Follow me, please. - Oh, okay.
你是"抽"明白了  還是"吸"明白了
Did you smoke or snort this clarity?
既然你這么好  送我新床單
Yeah, since you were nice enough to get me new sheets,
我也有東西作為回禮  給
I got you something in return. Here.
這是表示歉意的同時
Oh, is this like an apology,
兼表示謝意嗎
thank you kind of thing?
給我看好了
Now watch.
人接受禮物時就應該這么優雅
This is how one graciously accepts a gift.
這是啥玩意啊
What the hell is this?
假發
A wig?
不然就是你剝了80年代拉拉的頭皮
Either that or you scalped a lesbian from the '80s.
是的  我一把抓住她的波洛領帶
Yep, I grabbed her bolo tie
然后爬上她的墊肩[當年流行]
and climbed up on her shoulder pads.
你奪走讓我有安全感的東西
You took away my security thing--
我的枕套
the pillowcase--
所以現在我要奪走讓你有安全感的東西
So now I'm taking away your security thing--
你的頭發
your hair.
你今晚可以戴著那玩意
You can wear that on your head tonight
然后告訴我一切都只是心理作用可以克服
and then tell me again how this is all in my head.
你非得買人家店里最丑的那一頂嗎
Did you have to get the ugliest one they had?
3毛7的東西  你還想要求什么
What do you want for 37 cents?
好吧  我會把這個爛玩意頂頭上
Fine! I'll put this roadkill on my head
向你證明  我的價值不只是這頭秀發
Just to prove to you that I am so much more than my hair.
還有我的態度  心靈  大腦和勇氣
I am my attitude, my spirit, my brain, my bravery.
-戴上它  -麥克斯  我好害怕
- Put it on. - Max, I'm scared.
快  把劉海撥到后面[從后面搞]
Go. The bangs go in the back.
我就喜歡這種女人
That's my kinda woman.
科布沙拉  上菜
Cobb salad, pick-up!
蘇菲
Uh...hey, Sophie.
你是知道有黑手黨寡婦折扣  才穿著這樣嗎
Are you here for the mafia widow discount?
厄爾  我在保持低調
Earl, I'm incognito.
偷偷來給麥克斯送藥的
I'm making a drug drop for Max.
麥克斯  你的藥[毒品]來了
Hey, Max! I got your drugs!
謝啦
Thanks.
我愛死你永遠能找到一套
And I love that you have an outfit
適合我讓你干的事的衣服
for everything I ask you to do.
那個金發緝毒特警呢  麥克斯
Where's the blonde narc, Max?
天啊
Oh, my God!
卡洛琳加入保齡球隊了嗎
Did Caroline join a bowling team?
麥克斯  不行
Max! No!
糟糕
Aw, crap!
被羅德·斯圖爾特逮個正著
Rod Stewart just busted us.
英國老派搖滾歌手  發型類似
讓她爽一下吧  有啥大不了的  老古板
Let her have some fun. What's the big deal, square?
因為她覺得自己需要這藥的理由
The big deal is that Max thinks she needs these pills
是因為我丟了她的小被被
because I threw away her blankie.
那是個枕套  有它我才能睡著
It was a pillowcase, and I need it to sleep.
她得摸著才能睡
She has to rub it.
在波蘭
In Poland,
我也有樣小東西
I had this little thing that I liked to tickle
喜歡在睡覺前玩
before I went to sleep.
但也被我姨母扔了
But my aunt threw it away.
那是什么
What was it?
我的諾拉表妹
It was my cousin Nora.
-把藥給我  -不要
- Give me the pills. - Nope.
麥克斯  你是錯的  瞧我
And, Max, you were wrong. See?
我一點都不依賴我的頭發
I'm not attached to my hair.
老實說  我開始愛上我的新發型
In fact, I am loving my new look.
我是個懶得打扮的單親母親
Am I a single mom trying to keep it simple?
或是助理地方檢察官呢
Am I an assistant D.A. in over my head?
又或是邦·喬飛故事里的查理茲·塞隆
Or am I Charlize Theron in the Jon Bon Jovi story?
或許吧  我完全不介意
Maybe, and I'm fine with it.
因為我一點也不看重我的頭發
'cause I am not my hair.
天啊  火雞三明治帥哥  掩護我
Oh, my god, turkey club cutie! Hide me!
戴著難看的假發  雙膝跪地
On your knees in a bad wig.
姑娘  我也有過這樣的經歷
Listen, girl, I've been there.
不  我只是不想被人看見
No, I just don't wanna be seen.
卡洛琳  卡洛琳  我愛你
Caroline, Caroline, I love you,
但我聽不下去了
But I can't hear anymore.
這頂假發即使在70年代  也讓人不忍直視
That hair was hard enough to look at in the '70s.
好吧  你是對的  我是錯的
Fine! You were right, I was wrong.
幫我把假發脫下來  我不能讓他見我這樣
Now help me get this off. He can't see me like this.
沒錯  把藥給我
That's right, gimme the pills.
麥克斯  不  你不需要
Max, no. You don't need them.
我們都不知道這藥哪來的
We don't know where they've been.
好吧
Fine!
那我回家睡覺
I'm going home to try to sleep.
既然這都是你的錯  那你來替我上班吧
Since this is all your fault, you can finish my shift.
你自己上班吧
You're on your own,
80年代肥皂劇那個住在對面街的女人
lady who lived across the street from Al Bundy
不得不說  我真佩服我自己也能接發
I gotta say, I'm pretty impressed I can do this.
其實沒那么難嘛
It's not so hard.
我不懂錢妮絲干嘛老抱怨
I don't know what Chanice is always bitching about.
或許她就是個愛抱怨的賤人吧
I guess that's who she is.
真不敢相信我到現在還沒睡著
I can't believe I still haven't slept.
我這輩子都別想睡覺了
I'm gonna be awake forever.
最后會像那部電影《喚醒》  但我是想睡死過去
It's gonna be like that movie Awakenings, but not at all.
電影講述的是一名醫生在偶然的機會通過一種尚未通過臨床研究的藥物
使得病人走出了幾十年的夢境
麥克斯  你可以摸我
Max, you can rub me.
哇  那頂拉拉假發把你掰彎啦
Wow, that wig changed you.
不  是這里
No, here.
摸我睡衣下面的花邊
Rub the edge on the bottom of my jammie top
-把它當成是你的枕套  -不要
- like it's your pillowcase. - No.
如果我摸你睡衣的下面
If I rub the bottom of your jammies,
那我就會變成無下限
that would be my bottom.
火雞三明治帥哥沒有約我出去
Turkey club cutie didn't ask me out,
可能是因為我的頭發被假發弄得太亂了
probably because my hair was so messed up from the wig.
別對自己那么苛刻
Don't be so hard on yourself.
也有可能是討厭你性格啊
it could've been your personality too.
你真的覺得他是因為頭發才喜歡你嗎
You really think he only liked you for your hair?
反正我是
I only like me for my hair.
早說了吧  你就是愛它
Told you. You're attached to it.
我超級愛我的頭發
So attached to it!
用手轉著玩  甩著玩  翻著玩
Twirling it, tossing it, flipping it.
在我的脖子  肩膀還有后背感覺它
Feeling it on my neck, on my shoulders, on my back.
沒有光滑發髻的卡洛琳·錢寧
Caroline Channing without the option
就不是卡洛琳·錢寧了
of a sleek updo is not Caroline Channing.
對不起啦
And I'm sorry.
很抱歉我因為
I'm sorry I judged you
你對某物過于依賴而批評你
for having an attachment to something
而我也沒好到哪去
when I'm no better.
抱歉我把你親愛的寢具扔了
And I'm sorry I got rid of your sweet sheets.
麥克斯
Max.
Max?
晚安  麥克斯
Night, Max.
為什么啊
Whyyyy?
為什么我就不能擁有點好東西呢
Why can't I ever have anything nice?